avenuesocial.com 2012-06-14

# Privacy Policy | Avenue Social Inc.

.::Avenue Social::.

**What information do we gather?**

AvenueSocial has set this privacy plan to explain our policies regarding customer's personal data that is collected for our use. When you place a query online, you will only need to give some basic information to us by filling out a simple query form so that we could contact you to discuss the need. You will only need to enter your name, e-mail address, phone number or country.

**What do we use your information for?**

AvenueSocial uses the personal data for handling orders. AvenueSocial and its members also use your personal data and other personally non-identifiable information that will help us in handling your orders properly and to better respond to your complexity. Furthermore, your information may be used for the following ways: To improve our website features (by the feedbacks we receive from you) To keep you updated with our latest offers and happening To improve customer services.

**How do we protect your information?**

AvenueSocial uses a secure server for the purpose of securing your private information. All your private/credit information sends out via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology that is used to keep the information confidential when you place your order online.

**Do we use Cookie?**

We may use "cookies" for specific purposes which cookies are designed for. A cookie is a piece of information that the computer that hosts our Site gives to your computer when you access a website. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the Site and help us analyze Site usage more accurately.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include our subsidiaries and trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

Brands Get Social Using Avenuesocial
